Inventory of the Floyd Halleck Higgins Photographs of Mexican Sugar Beet Workers
Department of Special Collections
- Life in the labor camps, 1942; Series 3.; 57 prints and negatives
  - Five women entertainers facing camera, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0043; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:3)
    "Mexican-American artists ready for a show put on by U.S. sugar beet industry for the imported Mexican National harvest labor." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Five women entertainers facing camera, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0044; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Two women singing at microphone, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0045; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:3)
    "Mexican-American entertainers ready for their act at a theater in California where the Mexican Nationals imported for sugar beet harvest are brough [brought] from camps after work hours. Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Two women singing at microphone, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0046; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 10 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Two women singing at microphone, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0047; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Man playing piano, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0048; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 10 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Man playing piano, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0049; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
    "Sugar beet Mexican Labor entertainment. World War II. Spreckels, Woodland [California] area." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Man playing piano, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0050; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Man playing piano, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0051; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Man playing piano, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0052; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Three Mexican workers, holding hoes, looking at camera, near a building in Clarksburg, California, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0061; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Six Mexican workers standing beside building with hoes, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0064; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Group of Mexican workers with church in background, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0074; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Six Mexican workers standing beside building with hoes, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0087; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Two Mexican workers sitting in dining hall surrounded by other Mexican workers, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0088; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm (Box-folder 1:4)
    "In the dining room, a pair of Mexican hand ball players relax at Pleasanton, California over hot Mexican food cooked and served by Mexicans at a beet field labor camp. Better housing, better food, electric lights, clean dry and warm sleeping quarters, buses to mass on Sunday, trips to night baseball games, and night schools, where wanted, are some of the Good Neighbor innovations for Mexican workers announced by Manager J.E. Coke of California Fields Crops, Inc. in handling 3,000 imported Mexicans arriving to harvest the record beet crop in California this fall." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Dining hall with long tables and newly arrived Mexican workers standing at the chairs, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0089; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Six men eating in dining hall, cook in background, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0090; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Two Mexican workers signing a book, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0095; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 11 x 11 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Two Mexican workers signing a book, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0096; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Four Mexican workers eating in dining hall, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0097; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Woman and young man wearing cook's aprons beside camp building, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0098; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Woman and young man wearing cook's aprons beside camp building, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0099; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Woman and young man, who is holding a dog, wearing cook's aprons beside camp building, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0100; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
    "Even the Mexican boy waiter's dog is Mexican at this camp near Pleasanton. Cook and waiter pose outside the dining room as they get ready a hot dinner of nutritious Mexican dishes for the beet field hands." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Woman and young man who is holding a dog wearing cook's aprons beside camp building, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0101; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Young Mexican man and cook at a serving area, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0102; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
    "Happy Mexican cook and waiter ready to serve the hungry Mexican beet field workers as they arrive for dinner after a day's work and a hot shower." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, one man bowing, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0103; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, one man bowing, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0104; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, one man bowing, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0105; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, one man bowing, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0106; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 6 x 10 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, one man bowing, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0107; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0108; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Five men standing in front of a microphone, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0109; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Five Mexican workers in front of camp building, one worker holding a baby doll., 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0175; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:4)
- Harvesting the sugar beets, 1942; Series 4.; 83 prints and negatives
  The sugar beet harvest in 1942 was a bumper crop with no workers to harvest it because of World War II. California farmers asked the United States government to invite Mexico to send Mexican workers to California to help harvest the estimated 8 million hundred-pound bags of sugar beets. Three thousand workers were used to harvest the crop, topping and harvesting the sugar beets.
  - Two Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0053; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0054; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers topping sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0055; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    "Topping sugar beets after they are plowed out was one of the tough stoop labor jobs that the sugar beet harvester has eliminated." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Seven Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets beside a truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0056; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Three Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0057; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers picking up sugar beets to toss into truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0058; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Three Mexican workers picking up sugar beets to toss into truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0059; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Three Mexican workers topping sugar beets in Clarksburg, California, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0060; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Eight Mexican workers topping sugar beets in Clarksburg, California, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0062; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - One Mexican worker topping sugar beets in Clarksburg, California, 1942 Nov. 5; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0063; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0065; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942 Oct.; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0066; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers loading truck with sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0067; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers loading truck with sugar beets, one workers on top of truck. View from back of truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0068; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Four Mexican workers loading truck with sugar beets, one workers on top of truck. View from front of truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0069; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Three Mexican workers loading truck with sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0070; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Fourteen Mexican workers sitting on back of flatbed truck holding hoes, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0072; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Fourteen Mexican workers sitting on back of flatbed truck waving hoes, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0073; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Five Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0116; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Four Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0117; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Three trucks loaded with sugar beets entering Spreckels Sugar Company refinery, Woodland, California., 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0118; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 8 x 14 cm (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Four Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into a truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0127; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Many Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into a truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0128; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 16 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Four Mexican workers harvesting sugar beets beside a truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0129; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Three Mexican workers starting to toss sugar beets into a truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0130; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Two stooping Mexican workers and one standing Mexican worker tossing sugar beets into truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0131; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer leaning on a door of a truck loaded with sugar beets, business man looking on, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0132; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 8 x 13 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    "Spreckels Sugar Company, Woodland California." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Max Baer leaning on a door of a truck loaded with sugar beets, business man looking on, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0133; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 8 x 10 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer leaning on a door of a truck loaded with sugar beets, business man looking on, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0134; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer and Little Max sitting on a Mack truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0135; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 12 x 10 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    Spreckels Sugar Company, Woodland California. Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Max Baer waving while leaning on a Mack truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0136; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer standing next to a Mack truck, obtaining a receipt from the Spreckels Sugar Company, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0137; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer standing next to a Mack truck, obtaining a receipt from the Spreckels Sugar Company Refinery, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0138; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 8 x 9 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer talking with Spreckels Sugar Company executives, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0139; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 9 x 14 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer talking with Spreckels Sugar Company executives, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0140; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer unloading a truck full of sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0141; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 11 x 14 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer unloading a truck full of sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0142; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Max Baer Standing on runner of Mack truck, with business man looking on., 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0143; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer Standing on runner of Mack Truck, with business man looking on., 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0144; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Max Baer Standing on runner of Mack Truck, with business man looking on, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0145; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Five Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into a truck at Robert Barr's fields, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0146; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    "Mexican beet workers topping and loading sugar beets on Robert Barr's fields, Woodland, Calif., 4-42." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Five Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into a truck at Robert Barr's fields, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0147; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Many Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into a truck at Robert Barr's fields, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0148; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Robert Barr standing on the back of a truck with Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into the truck., 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0149; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    "President Robert Barr of the Central California Beet Growers' Assoc. And his crew of Mexicans recently imported into California to save the record crop. Mr. Barr likes the Mexican labor above all other for beet field work and says his crew had no trouble learning to top and load beets under his leadership, as they averaged 3 1/2 tons the first week and went up to 4 tons the second week." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Robert Barr standing on the back of a truck with Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into the truck., 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0150; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 9 x 14 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
    "Mexican beet workers topping and loading sugar beets on Robert Barr's Fields, Woodland, California, 4-42." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Robert Barr standing on the back of a truck with Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into the truck., 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0151; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Robert Barr standing on the back of a truck with Mexican workers tossing sugar beets into the truck., 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0152; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Spreckels Sugar Company refinery, Salinas, California, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0153; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
    "World's greatest beet sugar processing plant at Spreckels in the Salinas Valley, [California]." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Truck loaded with sugar beets unloading a sugar factory with sign, "Spreckels Honey-Dew Sugar", Manteca, California, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0161; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Front entrance of Spreckels Sugar Company, Manteca, California, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0162; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 14 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Spreckels Sugar Company, Manteca, California, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0163; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 14 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Spreckels Sugar Company refinery, Woodland, California. View from top of plant showing piles of sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0164; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 14 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Sugar beet pulp being loaded into a truck, Woodland, California, 1942 Oct. 22; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0165; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 10 x 14 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Sugar beet pulp being loaded into a truck, Woodland, California, 1942 Oct. 22; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0166; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Line of trucks going to Spreckels Sugar Company, Woodland California, 1942 Oct. 22; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0167; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Line of trucks going to Spreckels Sugar Company, Woodland California, 1942 Oct. 22; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0168; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Line of trucks going to Spreckels Sugar Company, Woodland California, 1942 Oct. 22; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0169; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Trucks loaded with sugar beets going down a road (rear facing) to Spreckels Sugar Company [Woodland, California], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0170; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 7 x 13 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Trucks loaded with sugar beets going down a road (rear facing) to Spreckels Sugar Company [Woodland, California], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0171; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Trucks loaded with sugar beets going down a road (front facing) to Spreckels Sugar Company [Woodland, California], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0172; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Three trucks loaded with sugar beets entering Spreckels Sugar Company refinery, Woodland, California, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0173; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Three trucks loaded with sugar beets entering Spreckels Sugar Company refinery, Woodland, California [close view], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0174; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - International Harvester Company crawler with cultivator in a field driven by a worker [tractor facing forward], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0176; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 8 x 14 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - International Harvester Company crawler with cultivator in a field driven by a worker [tractor facing forward], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0177; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - International Harvester Company crawler with cultivator in a field driven by a worker [close view], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0178; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
    Damage to center of negative
  - International Harvester Company crawler with cultivator in a field driven by a worker [tractor facing away], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0179; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 14 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - International Harvester Company crawler with cultivator in a field driven by a worker [tractor facing away], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0180; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Three Mexican workers waving hoes in sugar beet field, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0181; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Three Mexican workers hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0182; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0183; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 10 x 12 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
    "Mexican beet workers Robert Barr Fields, Woodland, California 4-42." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0184; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers with back towards camera hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0185; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Two Mexican workers with back towards camera hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942 April; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0186; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers hoeing in a sugar beet field, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0187; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field [One worker almost hidden], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0188; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field [One worker hidden], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0189; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 14 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
    "Stoop labor topping beets." Description by Hal Higgins.
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field [One worker hidden], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0190; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 18 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Two Mexican workers, side by side, hoeing in a sugar beet field [One worker hidden], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0191; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Robert Barr with four Mexican workers behind truck, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0192; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Two Mexican workers, one with a stocking cap, hoeing sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0193; 1 photograph: Gelatin Silver Print DOP: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Two Mexican workers, one with a stocking cap, hoeing sugar beets [different view], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0194; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Two Mexican workers, one with a stocking cap, hoeing sugar beets [second different view ], 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0195; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - One Mexican worker hoeing sugar beets, 1942; UCD.PIC.D494.2009.0196; 1 photograph: acetate negative: 13 x 19 cm. (Box-folder 3:8)